Katie Macleod

I'm an Integrated Graphic Designer currently living in East London. After being rewarded my degree in Edinburgh, I jumped straight into the fast-paced world of Advertising in the Big Smoke. I have now worked with a variety of clients, creating award-winning both digital and print work with a bunch of other talented people. I've been involved in all areas of the designers' agency life from video shoots to post-production, presenting to the client, conversing with build teams, and of course, the late night pitch jobs. I work on a daily basis with Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign and Sketch – although I am also proficient in Adobe Muse, Premiere Pro and Keynote.

Contact

07887 878746 katiemacleod94@hotmail.co.uk

http://katiemacleod.github.io

Work Experience

RAPP, London: Junior Graphic Designer June 2016 - Present From intern to lead designer on the PayPal account, RAPP gave me many responsibilites which allowed me to quickly learn the industry.

Freelance: Various Clients 2015 - Present Freelancing gives me the opportunity to improve my communication skills and confidence in pitching and presenting.

Wolffe, Edinburgh: Summer Placement August 2015 Wolffe was an insight into the life at a small design studio.

Tesco, Inverness: Customer Assistant June 2011 - February 2015 Working for over four years in one company taught me commitment to one team.

Summerhall: Art & Entertainment Venue December 2012 - April 2014 Immersing myself in a community of designers, artists and other talented people helped to build confidence networking.

Dynam Design Studio: Work Experience2010

By joining a design team as a teen I was able to understand the role and responsibilities of a designer from a young age.

During my most recent agency experience, I was given the opportunity to work with the following clients:

















Education

Edinburgh Napier University
Graphic Design BDes (Honours)

Zhengzhou University of Light Industry Semester for Student Exchange (China)

Inverness Royal Academy
1 Advanced Higher
5 Highers

1 Open University Course

Achievements

YCN Student Commendation
Our stand was 'Best in Show' at D&AD's New Blood
Gold Duke of Edinburgh Award
Black Belt (2nd Degree) in Tang Soo Do

Hobbies

Video-Editing, Photography, Travelling, Muay Thai, Kayaking, Uni-Cycling, Climbing, Hiking, Reading, Camping, Slack-lining, Skateboarding

Other Basics

Hometown: Inverness, Scotland Currently in: London, UK Date of Birth: 08/07/1994







Please visit my website to check out some of my work!